<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kbounce.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KOdbij</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kstuds</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBouncexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KBounce</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KBounce</name>
  <summary>KBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KBounce és un joc d'arcade de jugador únic amb elements de trencaclosques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KBounce és un joc d'arcade de jugador únic amb elements de trencaclosques</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">KBounce ist ein Arcade- und Rätselspiel für einen Spieler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Το KBounce είναι ένα παιχνίδι arcade για έναν παίκτη με τα στοιχεία ενός παζλ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">KBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">KBounce es un juego recreativo para un único jugador semejante a un rompecabezas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">KBounce on ühe mängijaga arkaadmäng mitmete mõistatuse elementidega</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KBounce, buruhausteko elementuak dituen jokalari-bakarreko arkupeko joko bat da.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">KBounce est un jeu d'arcade à un joueur qui intègre des éléments de puzzle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">KBounce é un xogo de arcada para un único xogador cos elementos dun quebracabezas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">KBounce adalah sebuah permainan arcade pemain tunggal dengan unsur teka-teki.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">KBounce è un gioco per un solo giocatore di tipo arcade ma con aspetti rompicapo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KBounce는 퍼즐 요소가 혼합된 단일 플레이어 아케이드 게임입니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KBounce is een arcade spel voor één speler met de elementen van een puzzel.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">KBounce er eit arkadespel med enkelte strategielement.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">KOdbij jest grą zręcznościową dla jednego gracza z elementami puzzli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KBounce é um jogo de arcada para um único jogador, com os elementos de um 'puzzle'</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">O KBounce é um jogo arcade de um jogador com elementos de quebra-cabeça</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">KBounce je arkádová hra pre jedného hráča s prvkami puzzle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">KBounce je arkadna igra za enega igralca z elementi sestavljanke</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Kstuds är ett arkadspel för en ensam spelare med inslag av problemlösning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">KBounce — це аркадна гра для одного гравця з елементами головоломки</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzlexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">KBounce 是一个带有解谜成分的单人街机游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">KBounce 是一款具有謎題元素的單人街機遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzle. It is played on a field, surrounded by wall, with two or more balls that move about in the field bouncing off of walls. The player can build new walls, decreasing the size of active field. The goal of the game is to fill at least 75% of the field and advance to the next level.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KBounce és un joc d'arcade de jugador únic amb elements de puzzle. Es juga en un camp rodejat per murs, amb dues o més boles que es mouen pel camp rebotant en els murs. El jugador pot construir murs nous, reduint la mida del camp actiu. L'objectiu del joc és omplir com a mínim el 75% del camp i així avançar cap al nivell següent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KBounce és un joc d'arcade de jugador únic amb elements de puzzle. Es juga en un camp rodejat per murs, amb dues o més boles que es mouen pel camp rebotant en els murs. El jugador pot construir murs nous, reduint la mida del camp actiu. L'objectiu del joc és omplir com a mínim el 75% del camp i així avançar cap al nivell següent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KBounce ist ein Arcade- und Rätselspiel für einen Spieler. Es wird auf einem von Wänden umgebenen Feld gespielt. Sie spielen mit zwei oder mehr Bällen, die an den Wänden abprallen. Sie können neue Wände bauen und damit die Größe des aktiven Spielfeldes einschränken. Ziel des Spiels ist es, mindestens 75 % des Spielfeldes auszufüllen und damit zur nächsten Ebene zu kommen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KBounce είναι ένα παιχνίδι για έναν παίκτη με τα στοιχεία ενός παζλ. Παίζεται σε ένα γήπεδο, περικλειόμενο από τοίχους, με δύο ή περισσότερες μπάλες που κινούνται στο γήπεδο και αναπηδούν στους τοίχους. Ο παίκτης μπορεί να ανυψώσει νέους τοίχους, μειώνοντας το μέγεθος του γηπέδου. Ο στόχος του παιχνιδιού είναι να γεμίσεις τουλάχιστον το 75% του γηπέδου και να περάσεις στο επόμενο επίπεδο.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzle. It is played on a field, surrounded by wall, with two or more balls that move about in the field bouncing off of walls. The player can build new walls, decreasing the size of active field. The goal of the game is to fill at least 75% of the field and advance to the next level.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KBounce es un juego recreativo para un único jugador semejante a un rompecabezas. Se juega en un campo, rodeado por un muro, con dos o más bolas que se mueven por el campo y rebotan en los muros. El jugador puede crear nuevos muros disminuyendo el tamaño del campo activo. El objetivo del juego es rellenar al menos el 75% del campo para poder avanzar al siguiente nivel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KBounce on ühe mängijaga arkaadmäng mõistatuse elementidega. Seda mängitakse seinaga ümbritsetud väljal, kus kaks või enam palli liiguvad ringi seinalt tagasi põrgates. Mängija saab rajada uusi seinu, vähendades nii kasutatava välja suurust. Mängu sihiks on hõivata vähemalt 75% väljast ja minna edasi järgmisele tasemel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KBounce, buruhausteko elementuak dituen jokalari-bakarreko arkupeko joko bat da. Sail batean jolasten da, hormaz inguratuta, bi pilota edo gehiago mugitzen dira hormetan punpaka. Jokalariak horma berriak eraiki ditzake, sail erabilgarriaren neurria txikiagotuz. Jokoaren helburua, gutxienez, saileko % 75 bete da eta hurrengo mailara iragatea da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KBounce est un jeu d'arcade à un seul joueur qui intègre des éléments de puzzle. Il se joue sur un champ entouré d'un mur, au sein duquel plusieurs boules rebondissent sur les murs. Le joueur peut construire de nouveaux murs, diminuant ainsi la taille du champ. L'objectif du jeu est de combler ainsi au moins 75% du champ afin de passer au niveau suivant.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KBounce é un xogo arcade para un xogador cos elementos dun quebracabezas. Xógase nun campo rodeado por unha parede e con dúas ou máis bólas que se moven polo campo botando contra as paredes. O xogador pode construír novas paredes, reducindo o tamaño do campo activo. O obxectivo do xogo é encher polo menos o 75% do campo e avanzar ao seguinte nivel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KBounce adalah sebuah permainan arkade pemain tunggal dengan unsur teka-teki. Ini dimainkan pada sebuah bidang, dikepung oleh dinding, dengan bola dua atau lebih yang bergerak mantul-mantul pada bidang dinding. Pemain bisa membangun dinding yang baru, mengurangi ukuran bidang yang aktif. Tujuan permainan adalah mengisi setidaknya 75% pada bidang dan maju ke level selanjutnya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KBounce è un gioco per un solo giocatore di tipo arcade ma con aspetti rompicapo. Viene giocato in un campo circondato da mura, con due o più palle che si muovono nel campo rimbalzando contro i muri. Il giocatore può erigere nuovi muri per ridurre il campo di gioco. Lo scopo del gioco è di rendere inattivo almeno il 75% del campo di gioco per passare al livello successivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KBounce는 퍼즐 요소가 혼합된 단일 플레이어 아케이드 게임입니다. 벽으로 둘러싸인 필드에서 진행되며, 벽에 맞으면 튕겨 나가는 두 개 이상의 공이 필드에 돌아 다닙니다. 플레이어는 새 벽을 세워서 필드 크기를 줄일 수 있습니다. 게임의 목표는 필드의 최소 75%를 채워서 다음 단계로 진행하는 것입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KBounce is een arcade spel voor een enkele speler met de elementen van een puzzel. Het wordt gespeeld op een veld, omringt door een muur, met twee of meer ballen die in het veld bewegen en botsen vanaf de muren. De speler kan nieuwe muren bouwen, waarmee de grootte van het actieve veld wordt verkleind. Het doel van het spel is om minstens 75% van het veld te vullen en door te gaan naar het volgende niveau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KBounce er eit arkadespel med enkelte strategielement. På det innmura spelebrettet sprett det rundt to eller fleire ballar, og du må byggja nye murer for å redusera plassen dei har til å spretta. Målet er å fylla opp minst 75 % av spelebrettet, slik at du kjem vidare til neste brett.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KOdbij jest grą zręcznościową dla jednego gracza z elementami puzzli. Gra się nią na polu otoczonym ścianami z dwiema lub więcej piłkami, które poruszają się po polu odbijając się od ścian. Gracz może zbudować nowe ściany, ograniczając przy tym rozmiar pola. Celem gry jest wypełnienie co najmniej 75% pola, tak aby przejść do następnego poziomu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KBounce é um jogo de arcada para um único jogador, com os elementos de um 'puzzle'. É jogado num campo rodeado por uma parede, com duas ou mais bolas que se deslocam no campo através de ricochetes nas paredes. O jogador poderá criar novas paredes, reduzindo o tamanho do campo activo. O objectivo do jogo é preencher pelo menos 75% do campo e passar para o nível seguinte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KBounce é um jogo arcade de um jogador com elementos de quebra-cabeça. É jogado em um campo, cercado por parede, com duas ou mais bolas que se movem sobre no campo batendo nas paredes. O jogador pode construir novas paredes diminuindo o tamanho do campo ativo. O objetivo do jogo é preencher pelo menos 75% do campo e avançar para o próximo nível.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KBounce je arkádová hra pre jedného hráča s prvkami puzzle. Hrá sa na poli, obklopenom stenou, s dvoma alebo viacerými loptičkami, ktoré sa pohybujú v poli, odrážajúcimi sa od stien. Hráč môže vytvárať nové steny, čím zmenšuje veľkosť aktívneho poľa. Cieľom hry je vyplniť najmenej 75% poľa a postúpiť na ďalšiu úroveň.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KBounce je arkadna igra za enega igralca z elementi sestavljanke. Igra se na polju, obdanem s steno, z dvema ali več kroglicami, ki se gibljejo po polju, ki se odbijajo od sten. Igralec lahko zgradi nove zidove in tako zmanjša velikost aktivnega polja. Cilj igre je zapolniti vsaj 75% polja in napredovati na naslednjo stopnjo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kstuds är ett arkadspel för en ensam spelare med inslag av problemlösning. Det spelas på ett fält, som omges av väggar, med två eller flera bollar som rör sig över fältet och studsar mot väggarna. Spelaren kan bygga nya väggar, vilket minskar det aktiva fältets storlek. Spelets mål är att fylla minst 75 % av fältet och gå vidare till nästa nivå.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBounce — аркадна гра із елементами головоломки для одного гравця. Гра відбувається на полі, яке обмежено стінками. Полем рухаються і відбиваються від стін дві або декілька кульок. Гравець може будувати нові стіни, зменшуючи розмір доступного для кульок простору. Метою гри є перекрити принаймні 75% площі ігрового поля для переходу на наступний рівень.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBounce is a single player arcade game with the elements of puzzle. It is played on a field, surrounded by wall, with two or more balls that move about in the field bouncing off of walls. The player can build new walls, decreasing the size of active field. The goal of the game is to fill at least 75% of the field and advance to the next level.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KBounce 是一个带有解谜成分的单人街机游戏。一般在一个由墙环绕的场地中进行游戏，其中有两个会在场地中四处移动并且会在墙壁上反弹的球。玩家可以建造新墙来缩小有效场地的面积。游戏目标为填满场地的75%来前进到下一关。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KBounce 是一款具有謎題元素的單人街機遊戲。它是在一個被牆壁包圍的場地進行，有兩個或兩個以上的球在牆壁間反彈。玩家可以建造新的牆來減少活動場地大小。遊戲目標是佔領至少75%的場地，然後進到下一個等級。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kde.org/applications/games/org.kde.kbounce</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbounce</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kbounce</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kbounce&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Jugant al KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">KBounce spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Παίζω KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Playing KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugando a KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">KBounce'i mängimine</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">KBouncekin jokatzen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Partie de KBounce en cours</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xogando a KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Memainkan KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Giocare a KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KBounce 플레이</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KBounce spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Spelar KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Granie w KOdbij</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogar ao KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogando KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hranie KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Igra KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela Kstuds</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying KBouncexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">游玩 KBounce</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KBounce 遊玩畫面</caption>
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/kbounce.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12"/>
    <release version="21.04.3" date="2021-07-08"/>
    <release version="21.04.2" date="2021-06-10"/>
    <release version="21.04.1" date="2021-05-13"/>
  </releases>
</component>
